Finding Aid for the Daniel C. Prince Papers and S.T.A.R. Collection
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Photographs
  - (Box 65)
    - Shapard, O.W. (Box D)
    - Sher, Alex (Box D)
    - Sidofsky, Hannah (Box D)
    - Sims, Bernice (Box D)
    - Smith, Jeff (Box D)
    - Smith, Lillian (Box D)
  - (Box 65)
    - Smith, Lillian (cont.) (Box E)
    - Smith, Mary (Box E)
    - Smith, Matthew (Box E)
    - Smith, Robert E. (Box E)
  - (Box 65)
    - Smith, Robert E. (cont.) (Box F)
    - Snyder, Bill (Box F)
    - Somerby, Richard (Box F)
    - Sorrento, Lamar (Box F)
    - Sottou, Jean (Box F)
    - Sowell, John (Box F)
    - Sparrow, Simon (Box F)
    - Speller, Henry (Box F)
    - Staples, Marcus (Box F)
    - Strausser, Dorothy (Box F)
    - Streeter, Vannoy (Box F)
    - Stoick, Rod (Box F)
    - Strelakos, George (Box F)
    - Stummer, Janis (Box F)
    - Sudduth, Jimmy Lee (Box F)
  - (Box 65)
    - Sudduth, Jimmy Lee (cont.) (Box G)
    - Sullivan, Dee (Box G)
    - Thomas, Sanford (Box G)
    - Thomsen, Arrahiwana (Box G)
    - Thweatt, Mary (Box G)
    - Tolliver, Mose (Box G)
    - Tompkins, Betty (Box G)
    - Toole, Maggie (Box G)
    - Townsend, Parks (Box G)
    - Toy, Randy (Box G)
  - (Box 65)
    - Toy, Randy (cont.) (Box H)
    - Turner, John (Box H)
    - Turner, Othar (Box H)
    - Vakili-Taleghani, Nasser (Box H)
    - Van Maanen, Gregory (Box H)
    - Veber, Suzan (Box H)
    - Virgous, Felix (Box H)
    - Walker, Inez (Box H)
    - Wallace, Clyde (Box H)
    - Wallin, H. (Box H)
- Photographs
  - (Box 66)
    - Wallin, H. (cont.) (Box A)
    - Walpert (Box A)
    - Washburn, Susan (Box A)
    - Webb, Lillian (Box A)
    - Webb, Troy (Box A)
    - Williams, Bob (Box A)
    - Williams, Darryl (Box A)
    - Williams, Jeff (Box A)
    - Womack, Barbara (Box A)
    - Wood, Beatrice (Box A)
    - Woodruff, Kristina (Box A)
    - York, Rhawn (Box A)
  - (Box 66)
    - York, Rhawn (cont.) (Box B)
    - Zeldis, Malcah (Box B)
    - Zimmerman, Drew (Box B)
    - Zimmerman, Eleanor (Box B)
    - Anonymous, Animals (Box B)
    - Anonymous, Children’s Art (Box B)
    - Anonymous, Collage (Box B)
    - Anonymous, Drawing (Box B)
    - Anonymous, Environments (Box B)
    - Anonymous, Faces and Figures (Box B)
    - Anonymous, Landscapes (Box B)
    - Anonymous, Other Media (Box B)
  - (Box 66)
    - Anonymous, Paintings (Box C)
    - Anonymous, Prisoner’s Art (Box C)
    - Anonymous, Sculpture (Box C)
    - Anonymous, Signs (Box C)
    - Anonymous, Unknown Artists from Cavin-Morris (Box C)
    - Anonymous, Unknown Artist from Kerry Schuss (Box C)
    - Anonymous, Wood Carving (Box C)
    - Anonymous, Danny (Box C)
    - Anonymous, Gretchen (Box C)
    - Anonymous, Maggie (Box C)
    - Anonymous, Sam (Box C)
    - Environments, Black, Calvin (Box C)
    - Environments, Ehn, John (Box C)
    - Environments, Finster, Howard (Box C)
    - Environments, Greco, John (Box C)
  - (Box 66)
    - Environments, Greco, John (Box D)
    - Environments, Lucas, Charlie (Box D)
    - Environments, Rice, W.C. (Box D)
    - Environments, Tassitano, Joe (Box D)
    - Environments, Tawana, Kea (Box D)
    - Environments, Warren, Frank (Box D)
    - Environments, Woitko, Joseph (Box D)
    - Environments, Zoettl, Joseph (Box D)
    - Exhibits, A Hand Has Five Fingers (Box D)
    - Exhibits, Art Across America (Fire and Krasner) (Box D)
    - Exhibits, Art Across America (Unidentified Artist) (Box D)
    - Exhibits, Basom College Show (Box D)
  - (Box 66)
    - Exhibits, Biggest, First Hanging (Box E)
    - Exhibits, Biggest, Second Hanging (Box E)
    - Exhibits, Biggest Collapsed Walls (Box E)
    - Exhibits, California Discoveries (Box E)
    - Exhibits, Collecting the Familiar (Box E)
    - Exhibits, Eureka! I Found It (Box E)
    - Exhibits, Flights of Fancy (Box E)
    - Exhibits, Flo Laffel Show (Box E)
    - Exhibits, Made to Last (Box E)
    - Exhibits, Made to Last, Prospective Pieces (Box E)
  - (Box 66)
    - Exhibits, Made to Last, Prospective Pieces (Box F)
    - Exhibits, MONY- Statue of Liberty Exhibit (Box F)
    - Exhibits, NY Psychiatric Show- Ben Apelbaum (Box F)
    - Exhibits, Leroy Person and Jonathan Williams Exhibit (Box F)
    - Exhibits, Railroad Exhibit (Box F)
  - (Box 66)
    - Exhibits, Rebuilding Liberty (Box G)
    - Exhibits, Thrift Shop Art Exhibit (Box G)
    - Exhibits, University Club of Nashville Exhibit (Box G)
    - Exhibits, Untitled Show in North Carolina (Box G)
    - Exhibits, We’re Moving Now- Olympic Show TULA (Box G)
    - Ethnographic Arts, General (Box G)
    - Ethnographic Arts, Haitian (Box G)
    - Ethnographic Arts, Huichol (Box G)
  - (Box 66)
    - Ethnographic Arts, Huichol (Box H)
    - Ethnographic Arts, Huichol (possibly sold) (Box H)
    - Ethnographic Arts, Inuit- Bone Carving (Box H)
    - Ethnographic Arts, Inuit- Wood Carving (Box H)
    - Ethnographic Arts, Inuit- Paintings (Box H)
    - Ethnographic Arts, Native American- Mixed Origin (Box H)
    - Ethnographic Arts, Native American- Pacific Northwest (Box H)
    - Ethnographic Arts, Native American- Southwest (Box H)
    - Subject Files, Arnett, Bill- Thorton Dial Works (Box H)
    - Subject Files, Lyles, TN Art Club (Box H)
- Photographs
  - (Box 67)
    - Subject Files, Book Tours (Box A)
    - Subject Files, Broken Pieces (Box A)
    - Subject Files, Cloverbottom Artists (Box A)
    - Subject Files, Diners (Box A)
    - Subject Files, Flooring (Box A)
    - Subject Files, G.R.A.C.E. (Box A)
    - Subject Files, Hemphill, Bert – House and Items sold to him (Box A)
    - Subject Files, Henshey’s (Box A)
    - Subject Files, Hiatt, John- at the Bottomline with STAR Art (Box A)
    - Subject Files, “Inventory” Photographs (Box A)
    - Subject Files, Israel Levin Center (Box A)
    - Subject Files, Misc. (Box A)
    - Subject Files, Museum of Appalachia (Box A)
    - Subject Files, Nigerian Truck Paintings (Box A)
    - Subject Files, Pacific Futures- California Artists in Communities- Pasadena (Box A)
    - Subject Files, Primm Springs (Box A)
    - Subject Files, St. Sophie’s (Box A)
  - (Box 67)
    - Subject Files, St. Sophie’s (cont.) (Box B)
    - Subject Files, Signs (Box B)
    - Subject Files, Southend Community Center (Box B)
    - Subject Files, Tokeneke School (Box B)
    - Sub-Series, Damage to the Biggest Exhibit (Box B)
  - (Box 67)
    - Sub-Series, Damage to the Biggest Exhibit (cont.) (Box C)
    - Sub-Series, Machine Models, Prospective Materials (Box C)
  - (Box 67)
    - Sub- Series, Artwork sold by Dan Prince (Box D)
      - Bajaj, Bindu (Box D, File 1)
      - Bathija, Jyoti (Box D, File 2)
      - Black, Calvin and Ruby (Box D, File 3)
      - Danek, Karolina (Box D, File 4)
      - Daniels, Virgil (Spot) (Box D, File 5)
      - Darling, Sanford (Box D, File 6)
      - Digney, Jerry (Box D, File 7)
      - Hawkins, William (Box D, File 8)
      - Jarrett, Alvin (Box D, File 9)
      - Haynes, Sam (Box D, File 10)
      - Holley, Lonny (Box D, File 11)
      - Killian, Helene (Box D, File 12)
      - Kristoff, Jessica (Box D, File 13)
      - Kristoff, Jessica (Box D, File 14)
      - Kristoff, Jessica (Box D, File 15)
      - Kristoff, Jessica (Box D, File 16)
      - Kristoff, Jessica (Box D, File 17)
      - Kristoff, Jessica (Box D, File 18)
      - Kristoff, Jessica (Box D, File 19)
      - Kristoff, Jessica (Box D, File 20)
      - Kristoff, Jessica (Box D, File 21)
      - Kristoff, Jessica (Box D, File 22)
      - Kristoff, Jessica (Box D, File 23)
      - Kristoff, Jessica (Box D, File 24)
      - Laga, William (Box D, File 25)
      - Langrock, David (Box D, File 26)
      - Pawlovsky, Elllia (Box D, File 27)
      - Perry, Eugene (Box D, File 28)
      - Prince, Dan (Box D, File 29)
      - Prince, Dan – Project Proposals, Large Photos and Photocopies (Box D, File 30)
      - Richards, Devron (Box D, File 31)
      - Ross, Alex (Box D, File 32)
      - Saussy, Ci Ci (Box D, File 33)
      - Schatz, Bernard (Box D, File 34)
      - Serl, Jon (Box D, File 35)
      - Smith, Robert E. (Box D, File 36)
      - Sparrow, Simon (Box D, File 37)
      - Streeter, Vannoy (Box D, File 38)
      - Zimmerman, Drew (Box D, File 39)
      - Anonymous (Box D, File 40)
      - Miscellaneous Artwork (Named Artists)- Black and White Photos, Negatives and Contact Sheets (Box D, File 41)
      - Miscellaneous Artwork and Artists- Color Transparencies (Box D, File 41a)
      - Environments- Wickham, Enoch Tanner (Box D, File 42)
      - Environments- Wickham, Enoch Tanner (Box D, File 43)
      - Exhibits- Miscellaneous (Box D, File 44)
      - Exhibits- Biggest and California Discoveries- Contact Sheet and Large Prints (Box D, File 45)
      - Exhibits- Biggest (Box D, File 46)
      - Exhibits- Rebuilding Liberty (Box D, File 47)
      - Ethnographic Arts- Hawaiian Petroglyphs (Box D, File 48)
      - Ethnographic Arts- Huichol (Box D, File 49)
      - Ethnographic Arts- Inuit (Box D, File 50)
      - Ethnographic Arts- Mexican Death Cart (Box D, File 51)
      - Subject Files- Primm Springs (Box D, File 52)
      - Subject Files, Projects- Mixed Projects, Large Size Color Photocopies (Box D, File 53)
      - Subject Files, Projects- Stamford Connecticut- Southend Community Center (Box D, File 54)
      - Subject Files, Projects- Sticks and Stones, Large Size Color Photocopies (Box D, File 55)
      - Subject Files- Venice Beach, CA- Murals and People (Box D, File 56)
- Slides
  - Sleeves 1-5 (Box 68, File 1)
  - Sleeves 6-12 (Box 68, File 2)
  - Sleeves 13-17 (Box 68, File 3)
  - Sleeves 18-24 (Box 68, File 4)
  - Sleeves 25-30 (Box 68, File 5)
  - Sleeves 31-36 (Box 68, File 6)
  - Sleeves 37-42 (Box 68, File 7)
  - Sleeves 43- 46 (Box 68, File 8)
  - Sleeves 47-52 (Box 68, File 9)
  - Sleeves 53-58 (Box 68, File 10)
  - Sleeves 59-64 (Box 68, File 11)
  - Sleeves 65- 70 (Box 68, File 12)
  - Sleeves 71-76 (Box 68, File 13)
  - Sleeves 77-82 (Box 68, File 14)
- Slides
  - Sleeves 83-89 (Box 69, File 1)
  - Sleeves 90-93 (Box 69, File 2)
  - Sleeves 94-95 (Box 69, File 3)
  - Sleeves 96-102 (Box 69, File 4)
  - Sleeves 103-106 (Box 69, File 5)
  - Sleeves 107-112 (Box 69, File 6)
  - Sleeves 113- 116 (Box 69, File 7)
  - Sleeves 117-121 (Box 69, File 8)
  - Sleeves 122-127 (Box 69, File 9)
  - Sleeves 128-131 (Box 69, File 10)
  - Sleeves 132-137 (Box 69, File 11)
  - Sleeves 138-143 (Box 69, File 12)
  - Sleeves 144-146 (Box 69, File 13)
  - Sleeves 147-152 (Box 69, File 14)
  - Sleeves 153-158 (Box 69, File 15)
  - Sleeves 159-161 (Box 69, File 16)
- Slides
  - Sleeves 162-168 (Box 70, File 1)
  - Sleeves 169-172 (Box 70, File 2)
  - Sleeves 173-177 (Box 70, File 3)
  - Sleeves 178-185 (Box 70, File 4)
  - Sleeves 185-190 (Box 70, File 5)
  - Sleeves 191-195 (Box 70, File 6)
  - Sleeves 196-200 (Box 70, File 7)
  - Sleeves 201-207 (Box 70, File 8)
  - Sleeves 208-212 (Box 70, File 9)
  - Sleeves 213-218 (Box 70, File 10)
  - Sleeves 219-225 (Box 70, File 11)
- Cassette Tapes
  - (Box 71)
    - Anne Ambrose - White Dove Theatre, The Music of Hope (Box A)
    - Anne Ambrose and David Dobson - Songs of the White Dove Theater, Open Up Your Heart (Box A)
    - Danny Dowler – Danny’s Annual Number One Songs 1966-1995, Accompanied by a booket (Box A)
    - Dan Prince – Harp, Rev, 12/17/80 (Box A)
    - Dan Prince – Hawaii. Rev. (Box A)
    - Dan Prince – Hawaiian, Rev, 12/12/79 (Box A)
    - Dan Prince – Jimi Coolbreeze 2/26 (Box A)
    - Dan Prince – Ras Quel 2/23 (Box A)
    - Harley Interview on WXPN, December 4, 1973 10PM (Box A)
    - Holyland U. S. A. – Radio-spot News June 1978 John Greco, Sr. Josephine, Sr. Angelica Valenti (Box A)
    - Huichol- Dancing Songs (Box A)
    - Kristin L. H. – Collage of Sound and Thought (compiled in Winter) (Box A)
    - Kristin L. H. – Hypnosis for Relaxation and Health *not to be used while driving (Box A)
    - Neubach Chaotic - Vomit Baby (Box A)
  - (Box 71)
    - Robert E. Smith –Accident at Rolla (Box B)
    - Robert E. Smith –Apartment Complex Farm Scene by River/ Betty and Randy’s Point (Box B)
    - Robert E. Smith –A Wild Day (Box B)
    - Robert E. Smith –Backyard in Santa Monica (Box B)
    - Robert E. Smith –Birds (Box B)
    - Robert E. Smith –Black Folks League (Box B)
    - Robert E. Smith –Bobaloo’s Golden Green Sports Car (Box B)
    - Robert E. Smith –Bobaloo’s Golden Yellow and Pink Cadillac (Box B)
    - Robert E. Smith –Bud’s Diner (Box B)
    - Robert E. Smith –Bunkerhill (Box B)
    - Robert E. Smith –Central High School, Home of the Bulldogs (Box B)
    - Robert E. Smith –Challenger Space Accident (Box B)
    - Robert E. Smith –Col. Sanders Kentucky Fried Chicken (Box B)
    - Robert E. Smith –Comisky Park of Chicago, 1943 (Box B)
    - Robert E. Smith –Crazy Artist (Box B)
    - Robert E. Smith –Dr. Fandango’s Office (Box B)
    - Robert E. Smith –Elm Street In Springfield (Box B)
    - Robert E. Smith –Elmer Fudd’s Garage Sale (Box B)
    - Robert E. Smith –Elmer Fudd’s Garage Sale (Box B)
    - Robert E. Smith –Elvis Presley (Box B)
    - Robert E. Smith –Elvis Presley in Las Vegas (Box B)
    - Robert E. Smith –Famous People and Roberto Smittyboob (Box B)
    - Robert E. Smith –The Fish Accident (Box B)
  - (Box 71)
    - Robert E. Smith –Flood Scene St.Charles, Mo. (Box C)
    - Robert E. Smith –Garage Sale in Desert/ Dan Prince’s Office (Box C)
    - Robert E. Smith –General Store (Box C)
    - Robert E. Smith –Grant’s Farm (Box C)
    - Robert E. Smith –Green Hornet’s Garage Sale (Box C)
    - Robert E. Smith –Hall of Fame (Box C)
    - Robert E. Smith –Horatio Smittyboob’s Health Club (Box C)
    - Robert E. Smith –Hugo’s Karate Class (Box C)
    - Robert E. Smith –Humane Society (Box C)
    - Robert E. Smith –Jethroe’s Pig Farm (Box C)
    - Robert E. Smith –Karate (Box C)
    - Robert E. Smith –Lady Bears Basketball Team (Box C)
    - Robert E. Smith –Laura Ingles Wilder Home (Box C)
    - Robert E. Smith –Library of Congress (Box C)
    - Robert E. Smith –Little Boy Doctor; An Artist in the Country/ ______ Land in Montana (Box C)
    - Robert E. Smith –More Mustard Please (Box C)
    - Robert E. Smith –More Mustard Please (Box C)
    - Robert E. Smith –Painting (Box C)
    - Robert E. Smith –Pattonville (Box C)
    - Robert E. Smith –Perry Mason Theme Song, Thanks for the Memory, other songs (Box C)
    - Robert E. Smith –Planet of the Apes (Box C)
    - Robert E. Smith –Plaza Neighborhood Albuquerque (Box C)
    - Robert E. Smith –Raiding Bears in Montana (Box C)
    - Robert E. Smith –Raiding Bears in Montana (Box C)
  - (Box 71)
    - Robert E. Smith –Rape in Walnut Grove (Box D)
    - Robert E. Smith –Rivertown USA (Box D)
    - Robert E. Smith –Roberto Smittyboob Wins Blue Ribbon at Fair (Box D)
    - Robert E. Smith –Rouen France (Box D)
    - Robert E. Smith –Sam’s Gas Hut (Box D)
    - Robert E. Smith – San Francisco Earthquake (Box D)
    - Robert E. Smith –Santa Gets Ready Small Town Bandstand (Box D)
    - Robert E. Smith –Somewhere in Alaska; Lexington, Mass.; Sam’s Karate/Halloween; Strange Day (Box D)
    - Robert E. Smith –Somewhere in the Sahara (Box D)
    - Robert E. Smith –St. Patrick’s Cathedral (Box D)
    - Robert E. Smith –Take Me Out to the Ballgame (Box D)
    - Robert E. Smith – Vanderbilt University (Box D)
    - Robert E. Smith –Venice California Hamlet and Macbeth/ Scene in Venice Italy (Box D)
    - Robert E. Smith –Veselka Coffee Shop (Box D)
    - Robert E. Smith –Welcome to Ghosttown (Box D)
    - Robert E. Smith –What Child is This (Box D)
    - Robert E. Smith –Wild Adventure (Box D)
    - Robert E. Smith –Wild Adventure (Box D)
    - Robert E. Smith –Wild X-Mas (Box D)
    - Robert E. Smith –Young and Restless (Box D)
    - Robert E. Smith – 5Stories (Box D)
    - Robert E. Smith – 5Stories (Box D)
    - Robert E. Smith – No 1 (Box D)
- Compact Discs
  - Robert E. Smith – Christmas Songs (Robert E. Smith Vocalist and Kelly Brown on Piano)
- T-Shirt
  - Save John Greco’s Holyland USA
- VHS Video Cassettes
  - Alvin Jarrett, 1/17/90 (Box 72)
  - White Dove Theater’s North Pole Blues, Written by David Dobson (Box 72)
  - Lonny Holley 7/12/90, Charlie Lucas 7/14/90, W. C. Rice 7/14/90 (Box 72)
  - Opening Venice 4/2/90 Robert E. Smith Survey and Interview (Box 72)
  - Anne Ambrose Art and Music (Peaceful Solutions) 4/94 (Box 72)
  - Dan Prince 1/10/91 Channel 12 (Box 72)
  - Prince Art Inventory, 9/11/92 (Box 72)
  - Larry Armistead/ John Jordan (Box 72)
  - Aaron Birnbaum talks about his art by Kerry Schuss, 1991 (Box 72)
  - Prince Art Edit (Box 72)
  - Ulysses S. Davis – High Museum Atlanta, in Barbershop in Savannah (Box 72)
  - Prince Art Gallery, Atlanta, GA, 1994 (Box 72)
  - New Britain Museum (Box 72)
  - Andy Kane with Lillian Kagan Atrium Show (Box 72)
  - Enchanted Garden (Box 72)
  - Joe Light (Box 72)
  - Freedom to Create-Painting 3-The Art Studio (National Institute of Art and Disabilities) (Box 72)
  - Light/Saraf 1st Dups, Grandma Prisbrey, Rolling Mt Thunder, Possum Trot (Box 72)
  - Copy of Broadcast From the Future (Box 72)
  - Creativity Explored of San Francisco (Box 72)
  - At Work, Jennifer’s Tape, Home Movies, Girlie Girls, Clarissa, Barbie Workout (Box 72)
  - Duke Ellington (Box 72)
  - Ray Librizzi, Karolina Danek (Box 72)
  - Dan Prince Life in America (Box 72)
  - Vannoy Streeter, 1/18/90 (Box 72)
  - Across America: Amazing Grace (Box 72)
  - Holyland USA, George Cotrona (Box 72)
  - Studio Tour/Bring Back/ Hiatt’s Place (Box 72)
  - Dan Prince-Lecture Museum of American Folk Art (Box 72)
  - The Claire Conway Show, 5/15/91 (Box 72)
  - Toyzini, 1992 (Box 72)
  - Anne Ambrose (Box 72)
  - A Man, A Bass, and A Box of Stuff #21 Starring Ritt Henn W/ Greg Pelner, 2/14/94 (Box 72)
  - Prince Gallery, 3/19/94 (Box 72)
  - Prince Art Inventory, Second Set, Tape II, 9/12/92, 9/14, 9/16 (Box 72)
  - El Spotro’s—El Spotros (Box 72)
  - Untitled (Box 72)
  - Untitled (Box 72)
  - Untitled (Box 72)
  - Untitled (Box 72)
  - Untitled (Box 72)
  - Mark La Feminas’ Showreel (Box 72)
  - Ray Librizzi, Lonny Holley, Karolina Danek, Larry Armistead (Box 72)
  - Jodi Wille, Director’s Showreel – Wool, “Kill the Crow”;The Mices, “Daddy’s Gone To California”; The Ex-Idols, “Social Kill”; R.E.M., “Find the River” (Box 72)
- VHS Video Cassettes
  - James Brown June 10, 1991, Live, Living in America (Box 73)
  - Benny Goodman (Box 73)
  - Prince Art Inventory, 9/11/92 (Box 73)
  - Prince Art Consultants Inventory (Box 73)
  - Amish (Box 73)
  - Gayleen (Box 73)
  - Blank with post – it note – Paint by #, Jerk, record over (Box 73)
  - Homer Green, Castlewood, Robert E. Smith-Venice Opening, 4/2/90 (Box 73)
  - Prince Art Consultants (Box 73)
  - Environmental Art in Ojai (Box 73)
  - Ann Krasner art work, 1995-1997 (Box 73)
  - Local H “Cynic” Directed by Jodi Wille 2/95 (Box 73)
  - San Bernadino Museum- Alex Ross, An Exhibition of American Primitive Paintings (Box 73)
  - Unlabeled cassette from Robert E. Smith – from envelope postmarked, 12/10/96 (Box 73)
  - University Club April – Sept 1998, A Good Likeness- Part II Portraits- D. Prince (Box 73)
  - The Art of Spot Daniel (Box 73)
  - Mark Walker: A Mendocino County Portrait, Copyright by Mendocino County Museum, 1988 (Box 73)
  - El Spotro- I minute egg- Lion Auction Industrial (Box 73)
- Hi 8 Video Cassettes
  - California Discoveries, 1993
  - Unlabeled
  - Unlabeled
- Magnetic Reel to Reel Tapes
  - Untitled
  - Untitled
  - Untitled
  - Untitled
- Professional Video Cassette
  - John Hiatt – Bring Back Your Love To Me
- Professional Video Cassettes
  - Dan Prince #1 (Box 74)
  - Dan Prince #2 (Box 74)
  - Dan Prince #3 (Box 74)
  - Dan Prince #4 (Box 74)
  - Master - Blacked and T. C. (Box 74)
  - 2nd Master a) edited with Titles b) Color Correct c) Slight audio dif, glitches, etc. (Box 74)
  - Slides (Box 74)
  - Environments -- Sanford Darling, Possum Trot, Grandma Prisbrey, Rolling MT Thunder (Box 74)
  - Untitled (Box 74)
  - Untitled (Box 74)
  - SEDA Tape A (Box 74)
  - SEDA Tape B (Box 74)
- Computer Disks (Macintosh)
  - Applications
    - Inventory, SBA doc, Address Lists, excel, Backup Discs. Misc
    - Customer/Artist Correspondence (2) 5/95
    - Correspondence Customer, Artist 10/94 – 5/95
    - Prince Art Address Lists, excel, Passing Mailing lists
    - Passing in the Outsider Lane, Promo, Show Lists
    - The Biggest
    - California Discoveries
    - Excel - Inventories, Book Sales/Orders
    - Star Documents
    - Touchbase Pro, Connecticut Files, Hospital Files
    - Inventory – L.A., Connecticut, Tennessee, Dan Prince Collection
    - SBA Documents, 2 STAR.Doc Backup
    - Financial Reports / Documents, Schedules
    - STAR. Doc, Foundations, Grants
    - Financial Reports 12/95
  - Passing, Artist Bios, Exhibit.doc
    - Good Likeness. Exhibit Copy, PR, Bios, Pricelists, Signage, Consignment Form, Inventory
    - Bios, California Discoveries, Biggest
    - Good Likeness Bios
    - Good Likeness Bios Backup
    - Quark- Bios/Work Bios
    - Quark – Newsletter, Press Release, Invite, Bill of Sale, Follow-up Letter, bill of sale entry format
    - Back up, Good Likeness Invite, Etc.
    - Gallery Bios (California Discoveries) in various Formats
    - IBM – Richards Disc- Bios – Bell, Quatch, Fuller, Hernandez, Zimmerman, Earl
    - Prince Article – Good Likeness Edit 1 Edit 2, Mary’s Stuff
    - “Katie” Prince “Original “MS” Disk”
    - Edit 2-4 Karolina, Randy, Howard, L15, Rhawn, Spot, CiCi, Jo, Jefferey D., Homer, Alvin, Finster, Danak, Stephie, Ray Lib, Passing.doc1
    - Tuttle Correspondence, Passing.submit2, 3/95
    - Passing in the Outsider Lane, First Submit
  - Dan’s MAC SE Backup
    - Dan Prince- System Folder and System Items
    - Dan Prince- Contents of “Word Commands” File from “Word” File
    - Dan Prince
    - Dan Prince- Contents of “Word Commands” File from “Word” File
    - Dan Prince
    - Dan Prince- Word and Excel Preferences, Put in “Preferences” File
    - Dan Prince- Word Documents from Word 5.1 Folder
    - Dan Prince- Excel Tutorial and Macro Library
    - Dan Prince
    - Dan Prince
    - Dan Prince- Contents of “Word Commands” File from “Word” File
    - Dan Prince- 5.1
  - Unlabeled box
    - Macintosh Basics, Computer Transfer 1/96
    - Getty Info
    - Dan’s Excel for The Biggest
    - Dan Prince
    - Microsoft Word 5.1, Backup, Gook Likeness info, Tuttle Correspondence, SBA Correspondence
    - Applications I- Calendar Maker, Kaleidograph, MacDraw II, Superlab
    - Screensaver and Calendar Viewer
    - Applications II – Microsoft Word 4.0, MacProject II
    - Adobe Photoshop
    - Prince Art Revised- Inventory (1995) 5/95, Receipts (4th Quarter’94), Expenses (4th Quarter of’94)
    - HP Deskwriter Series – Driver Install Disk
    - DeskWriter Installation Disk
    - Dan Backup, Address Lists Newsletter 2 STAR Doc
    - Inventory (Old Backup) 4th Quarter Receipts
    - Super Paint
    - Excel
  - File- Loose Disks-
    - 3 ½ inch disks
      - Ehrlich.txt
      - Superpaint
      - Excel
      - Untitled
    - 5 ¼ inch disks
      - Wordperfect 5.1, Prince/Artist Data by Liberman, 3/31/93
      - Poster Dan’s Art
      - No bad sectors, formatted
      - The Biggest – Art Show Labels, Titles for April 1, 1993 Show
- Negatives
  - Sleeves 1-10 (Box 75, File 1)
  - Sleeves 11-21 (Box 75, File 2)
  - Sleeves 22-30 (Box 75, File 3)
  - Sleeves 31-40 (Box 75, File 4)
  - Sleeves 41-50 (Box 75, File 5)
  - Sleeves 51-60 (Box 75, File 6)
  - Sleeves 61-71 (Box 75, File 7)
  - Sleeves 72-80 (Box 75, File 8)
  - Sleeves 81-91 (Box 75, File 9)
  - Sleeves 92-100 (Box 75, File 10)
  - Sleeves 101-110 (Box 75, File 11)
  - Sleeves 111-120 (Box 75, File 12)
  - Sleeves 121-130 (Box 75, File 13)
  - Sleeves 131-140 (Box 75, File 14)
  - Sleeves 141-151 (Box 75, File 15)
  - Sleeves 152-160 (Box 75, File 16)
  - Sleeves 161-170 (Box 75, File 17)
  - Sleeves 171-180 (Box 75, File 18)